Social services, equipment, urban services,
urban planning, roadworks, events ...
Each administration has many data
which may be of economic, social,
health or environmental interest,
thus are intended to be shared.
Problem :
How to make accessible
this mass of information in a simple and
attractive way, and with a tight budget?
With Datami, make your data
an asset for your territory,
a tool to dialogue with your audiences,
while meeting the requirements
of the (french) "Law for a Digital Republic".
Concretely ? Datami offers you
a data editing and formatting tool,
open source, free and does not require
in-depth computer skills.
Datami allows you to edit and update
your data in a few clicks.
You can then view them as
maps,
diagrams,
list of cards,
and then share them on any website
thanks to a simple widget.
Datami also offers you the possibility
to improve your datasets
thanks to its collaborative features.
You can invite your employees
or your community to contribute,
by enriching or correcting your data,
before your validation.
And if necessary, the datami team
can offer you personalized support
from defining your project
until the installation of datami on your site
So you too, with Datami,
Reconnect your data to your territory!